# AL-waleed Nasr eldin suliman nemer

Creative Web Developer offering 6+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions . Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Web Developer.

# Web Developer

## **Work Experience**

### Practical experience: Web Developer, Sep 2017 - Present

August 2017 - current | Remote

- Manage website development projects from initial design through to completion, improving cross-browser and cross-platform compatibility.
- Work closely with programmers and clients to meet project requirements, objectives and required functionality.
- Develop and integrate custom themes in WordPress and opencart.
- Enable site-wide promotions by programming HTML5 canvases to animate particles on web backgrounds.
- Conducting customer training on website content management systems

#### Web Developer, June 2017 - August 2021

- Developed websites from front to backend using PHP, JavaScript, and HTML.
- Enhanced user experience and accomplished webpage objectives by creating site structure, navigation, page optimization, and graphics integration.
- Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.
- Designed and maintained both corporate and client websites, using scripting languages and content management systems including WordPress.

#### Skills

- HTMI
- CSS
- Javascript
- bootstrap4

- React.js
- php
- python
- django
- laravel
- wordpress
- opencart

## **Education**

## .SHonors Degree: Honors (GPA: 2.45/4.0)

# **Computer Science**

Shendi University

JUNE 2016 - AUGUST 2021 | sudan, shendi